感谢大家
Thank you, everyone,
关门后特意留下来学习新的iPad点餐系统
for staying late to learn our new iPad order system.
我们没得选啊 你把大门从外面锁上了
We had no choice, you locked the door from the outside.
不论如何 都能学习嘛
Either way, we're learning.
阿憨 为什么要换新世纪点餐系统呢
Han, why would we update our order system
我们的制服来自20世纪70年代
when our uniforms are from the 1970's
而工资水平则停留在19世纪
and our paycheck is from the 1800s?
来开始教学吧
Let's get to the tutorial.
麦克斯 你得跟我角色扮演一下
Max, you and I are going to role-play.
行啊 你当小贱人
All right, you can be the little bitch,
我当我自己
and I'll be me.
我不需要学这个
I don't need this lesson.
触摸屏我熟到不行
I'm very familiar with the touch screen.
谷哥的"哥"叫的就是我
Let's just say I put the "Goo" in Google.
我来扮演一个要点餐的客人
I'm going to pretend I'm a customer,
要点一个汉堡
and order a hamburger.
你好 小姐 我想点一个汉堡
Hello, Miss. I'll have a hamburger.
没问题 小姐
Certainly, Miss.
您的汉堡要加 还是不加沙门氏菌呢
Would you like that with or without Salmonella?
阿憨 我学用iPad的第一堂课是乔布斯教的
Han, I got my first lesson on the iPad from Steve Jobs,
而现在居然沦落到憨不湿来教
and now I'm getting it from Han Jobs?
卡洛琳 别装得好像你比我更懂科技小玩意
Caroline, don't act like you know more about gadgets than me.
昨日美国土大款赢不过今日亚洲科技宅
Formerly rich doesn't beat currently Asian.
来吧 大家看看手里的iPad
Now, come on, everyone look at their iPads.
什么iPad 我没见到有iPad啊
What iPad? I didn't see an iPad
什么 不是吧
What? No.
有人说了什么跟iPad有关的事吗
Did somebody say something about an iPad?
iPad是啥呀
What the hell is an iPad?
它们都上哪去了
Where did they all go?
上拍卖网站转卖了吧
I'm guessing eBay.
快把全部都还回来 尤其是我那台
I want them all back, especially mine.
我正跟一位澳洲女性玩小暧昧呢
I'm in a casual flirtation with a woman in Australia.
她有部分原住民血统 但是性格真的很好
She's part aboriginal, but has a great personality.
给你哟 厄尔
Here you go, Earl.
麦克斯 出啥事了
Max, what's wrong?
你看起来很开心
You seem happy.
我只是还处在
I'm just still on a high
上周拿到一万块银行贷款
from this $10,000 bank loan I got last week.
以及在04年吃的"加料"布朗尼的兴奋劲上
And from an almost certainly laced pot brownie I ate in 2004.
真不敢相信你跟卡洛琳的小蛋糕生意
I can't believe you and Caroline got a bank loan
居然能申请到银行贷款
for your cupcake business,
而且没有任何无辜民众被你们抓去人质
and not a single hostage was involved.
麦克斯 你没有一万块
Max, you don't have $10,000.
你连付费网络频道会员都没有
You don't even have Netflix.
这笔钱是要付给帮我们做蛋糕T恤的工厂
This money is to pay a factory to make our cupcake T-shirts,
而我已经把工厂名单缩减到最后三家了
and I've whittled it down to three.
大家好
Hello.
说到"缩减"版
Speaking of whittled.
某人用了我的打印机 我猜是卡洛琳
Someone used my printer, and I'm guessing it's Caroline,
因为是跟生意有关的内容
'cause it's about business
而不是厄尔整天打印的安其拉·贝瑟拼贴图
and not another one of Earl's Angela Bassett collages.
我能说啥 一日贝瑟狗 终身贝瑟狗
What can I say, man? I'm a Bassett hound.
谢谢了 阿憨
Oh, thanks, Han.
这是我最近在研究的几家工厂
These are the factories I've been researching.
我希望我们的T恤是美国制造
We want our T-shirts to be American made.
我也有个美国女佣[音似]
I have an American maid,
她唯一很会做的就是吃我的早餐谷麦棒
and all she's good at is eating my granola bars.
麦克斯 我找到了一家就在布鲁克林这里的
Look, Max, I found one right here in Brooklyn.
"美国王牌[艾斯] 创办人艾斯·哈德威克
"American Ace. The founder, Ace Hardwick,
致力于妥善照顾员工"
is devoted to treating his workers well,"
而且不是AA美国服饰的那位变态佬那种"照顾"
and not in a creepy way like that American Apparel guy.
你的意思是他旗下的那些员工
So you're saying none of these workers
都没有被人的裤中王牌"爱湿"过吗
have ever found an Ace in their hole?
我在很多工厂里工作过
Look, I've worked in a lot of factories.
里头的猫腻我太清楚了
I know what goes on.
我在大衣工厂工作过
I worked in a coat factory,
所以现在我的肺里裹上了一层石棉
which is why my lungs are coated in asbestos.
我也曾经在内衣工厂里工作过
I worked in an underwear factory,
"内"里的人会克扣我劳动成果换来的工钱
where I was underpaid for the fruits of my looms,
而我工作过最烂的工厂呢
and worst factory of all,
是"起司工厂"
The Cheesecake Factory.
要不我们明天去工厂里看看
How about we do a walk-through tomorrow
确保里面一切妥当
to make sure it's up to snuff?
如果那里有鼻烟[妥当]
Well, if they have snuff,
我们应该立刻就去啊
why are we waiting till tomorrow?
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我有件好事要分享
Oh, hey. Hi, great news!
我在酒吧餐厅被查身份证看是否成年呢
I just got carded at Buffalo Wild Wings!
真的吗 我倒是在那里被人查到赶了出去
Really? I got carted out of there once.
还有另一件好消息
And more great news:
我在开始一项新业务
I'm starting my own new business.
你们的那一万块还在吗
So girls, you know how you have that $10,000?
我也不想一次把你们清光
Well, I don't want to clean you out,
不过你们觉得扔个九千五如何
but how do you feel about tossing me $9,500?
你们俩真应该投资 她这项新业务超棒
You two should invest. Sophie's business is genius.
你知道很多女性会把下面那里的毛
You know how a bunch of ladies got their down-there-hair
做手术激光永久除毛吗
permanently lasered off?
但原来的除毛师会用"迈·切"的表情看你们
Yeah, that's when your waxer gives you a Michael Chiklis.
苏菲能提供一种产品
Well, Sophie's offering a product
让你的"不毛之地"再度"枝繁叶茂"
that puts grass back on your field.
生意个毛 这种事关别人毛事啊
That's not a business. That's nobody's business.
是啊 我也不搞这种事
Yeah, I don't do any of that stuff.
我往上套个毛束就算完事了
I just throw a scrunchie on mine and go.
这事是有市场需求的 比如大雾视野不佳时
Hey, there's a need for this. Sometimes, in the fog,
我的飞"鸡"得看到"跑道" 才知去哪"降落"
my plane gets lost without a landing strip.
我们不干
We're out.
别这么快做决定啊 姑娘们
Oh, don't decide yet, girls.
你们都还没听到我取的有爱生意名呢
you haven't even heard the cute, little name.
"苏菲·科臣斯基的逼假发"
"Sophie Kuchenksi's Vagina Wigs!"
我们真心不想干
Yeah, we're really out.
这是可是优质产品
Oh. But it's a quality product,
是从"逼朝"进口的真人毛发产品呢
and it's real hair imported from "Va-China."
这辈子从未这么不想干一件事
Yeah, never been further out.
这里是我们的主楼层
And this is our main floor.
这里真棒
Wow, this is amazing!
感觉就像在威利旺卡的巧克力工厂里
I feel like we're in the Willy Wonka Factory.
可不是嘛
I know, right?
我们美国王牌的生意格言就是"欢乐工作"
The American Ace motto is "Work is fun."
麦克斯本来以为会是另一种工厂
Max was expecting a different kind of factory.
多点折磨 少点欢乐
More torture, less foosball.
可不是嘛 但我们美国王牌不这样
I know, right? Not at American Ace.
佩吉 你在这里的职位是什么呢
And what is your position here, Peggy?
是专门负责说"可不是嘛"的人吗
Are you the "I know, right?" person?
可不是嘛
I know, right?
不是 我是其中一位股东
No, I'm one of the owners.
我也负责染T恤
Also, I dye T-shirts.
员工在工作六个月后 可以拿到公司股份
See, every employee gets a percentage of the company after six months,
所以你待得越久 股份就"变"得越多
so the longer you stay, the more it grows.
我们在餐厅工作四年了
We've been at the diner four years,
唯一看到会"变"大的只有奥列格的裤裆
and the only thing we've seen grow is Oleg's pants.
可不是嘛
I know, right?
艾斯在等你们了 去吧 去欢乐一番
Well, Ace is expecting you. Go ahead, go have fun!
别被这表面景象给欺骗了
Hey, don't be fooled by what's on the surface.
就像你外表看起来是白富美
You look like you have money,
但你里面的底裤早破成千丝万缕
but I know your underwear's in shreds.
不是千丝万缕 是一丝一毫好吗
Not shreds, Max, shred.
一丝勇敢的内裤君从前面连到后面
Just one, it goes from front to back.
您好 我们该直接进来吗 门没关
Um, hi, should we just come in? The door is open.
是的 一直都这样
Yep, always is.
有门就会有隔阂 隔阂最煞风景了
Doors create boundaries. Boundaries are a bummer.
你知道还有什么事很煞风景吗
You know what else is a bummer?
大个子小鸡鸡吗
Tall guys with small penises?
是你们错过了冰淇淋跟好咖啡的推车啦
That you just missed the gelato and designer coffee cart.
要咖啡果仁夹心冰淇淋吗
Espresso hazelnut praline?
我们不是来吃冰淇淋的
We're not here for gelato.
我们不是来不吃意式冰淇淋的
We're not not here for gelato.
赞 见到你们真是太赞了
Awesome. It's awesome to meet you.
我是艾斯·哈德威克
I'm Ace Hardwick.
听好了 王牌艾斯
Look, "Ace",
我们给你这一万块钱
we're not about to give you $10,000
不是让你可以占心情不好的未成年女员工便宜
so you can take advantage of a sad, underage girl worker
就是卸货区附近 那个胸器逼人
near the loading docks 'cause her boobs are crazy big
需要人送回家的姑娘
and she needs a ride home.
我只是"打个比方"
That's a "for instance."
什么意思
I'm sorry?
艾斯 麦克斯对工厂有些信任上的问题
See, Ace, Max has some trust issues when it comes to factories,
所以我们今天来...
so, we're here today to--
感觉你快要连纸杯一起吃掉了
You're pretty much eating cardboard there.
要不要我再给你来一杯
You want me to get you another?
你应该看看她吃鲔鱼罐头的样子
You should see her with tuna cans.
我看到意大利熏火腿的推车了
Hey, I see the prosciutto cart.
有人想吃进口火腿吗
Who wants imported ham?
我
Me!
我们也不是来不吃熏火腿的啊
Well, we're not not here for prosciutto.
你们知道什么事很酷吗
Hey, you know what's cool?
矮个子大鸡鸡吗
Short guys with big penises?
你真有趣
You're fun.
美国王牌是你们生意的最佳选择
Your business belongs here at American Ace.
来吧 我带你们见见这个大家庭
Come on, let's go meet the family.
这男的有点惊到我了
That guy kind of creeps me out.
不过好的是 我终于可以见到我的家人了
On the plus side, I finally get to meet my family.
我设计这个空间就是让大家有开放的能量
I had this space designed for open energy
以及开放性的交流
and open conversation.
其他的老板们 你们好吗
What's up, other owners?
艾斯 你好吗
What's up, Ace?
我们的业绩成长了400%呢
Our sales, by 400%!
麦克斯 就是这里了 我们要的工厂
Max, this is it. This is our factory.
这里的员工们看起来又开心又成功
The employees look happy and successful.
超级男孩的成员也是啊
So did the members of 'N Sync.
但舞台帷幕的背后 两眼泪汪汪啊
but behind the curtain, a veil of tears.
卡洛琳 熏火腿推车在这里呢
Hey, Caroline, here's the prosciutto cart.
谢谢 艾斯
Thanks, Ace!
你慢慢享用 我去旁边做个快速五分钟按摩
Enjoy. I'm just gonna get a quick five-minute chair massage.
来吧 赶紧趁着艾斯去旁边把他脑袋
Come on, let's slip out while Ace has got his head
塞进椅子的屁股里时开溜吧
stuck in that chair's ass.
你们好啊
Hey, what's up?
欢迎来到美国王牌 我是里科
Welcome to American Ace. I'm Rico.
你真的真的真的很漂亮
You're, like, really, really, really pretty.
总之呢 我也是股东之一 还负责打扫厕所
So anyways, I'm part owner, and I clean the bathroom.
问个小问题 你们这边有红酒吗
Hmm, quick question: do you have a light Cabernet?
更小的问题
Quicker question:
你们藏着小童工的秘密房间呢
where's the secret room with the toddler slaves?
你好吗 我叫劳乌 股东之一兼保安
What's up? I'm Raul, part owner and security guard.
你们两位有空要一起喝杯东西吗
Hey, you two want to grab a drink sometime?
周五下班后 一起去隔壁的墨西哥薄饼店坐坐
Fridays after work, we all hang next door at Tortilla Flats.
墨西哥薄饼 那不是你的脱衣舞男艺名吗
Tortilla Flat. Wasn't that your stripper name?
你只是在嫉妒我的这个比较高
You're just jealous 'cause mine's taller
而且觉得我真的真的真的很漂亮
and thinks I'm really, really, really pretty.
祝你不会遇上大个子小鸡鸡
Good luck with that tall guy scenario.
抱歉迟到了 但我们要忙我们的其他生意
Sorry we're late, but we were busy with our other business,
就是我们在乎的那个
the one we care about.
你们这么"真诚衷心"的道歉 我哪会生气
How can I be mad with that sincere, heartfelt apology?
谁想看看我们的T恤样品
Who wants to see our sample T-shirts?
我想看 但我想看的东西太多了
I want to see it, but I want to see a lot of things.
但我有这白内障 我最多也就能
With these damn cataracts, the best I can do
往你们的方向看 看个白白的大概
is look towards it and get a milky idea.
姑娘们
Hey, girls!
我想给你们看看我新的
I want to show you some of my new styles
"周末欢乐必备阴发"系列产品
for my "Everybody's Merkin for the Weekend" Collection.
苏菲 什么是阴发
Sophie, what's a merkin?
是阴部假发
It's a vagina wig.
真是"肮脏"
Oh, that's dirty.
阿憨 我需要你提供点建议
And Han, I'm gonna need your input,
因为我在做亚洲的产品线
because I'm working on an Asian line.
阿憨不应该先自己长过
Shouldn't Han grow some hair on his
才有资格提建议吗
before he starts tossing out advice?
阿憨 我想知道我的产品质地是否正确
Han, I need to know if I got the texture right,
所以你过来
so come over here.
这就对了
Oh, yeah.
这感觉真赞
Yeah, that feels nice. Ohh.
又好又粗 在我指间摩擦
Yeah, nice and thick between my fingers.
赞啊
Oh, yeah.
慢点
Slower.
再慢点
Slower still.
这感觉像在看只沙鼠在搞一根铅笔
This is like watching your gerbil hump a pencil.
跟性不太有关 但一样能恶心死你
Not really sexual, but still grosses you out.
苏菲 我觉得你该停手了
Sophie, I-I think you should stop.
这酸爽的感觉打从三年级时
I haven't felt this sensation since third grade
女老师检查我的头虱后就再没有过了
when Madam Yi checked me for head lice.
提醒我明天帮阿憨买一本《我的身体怎么了》
Remind me to pick up a "What's Happening To My Body?"
健康教育书籍
book for Han tomorrow.
姑娘们 我就坐这儿
Oh, girls, I'll be over here,
研究我的非裔美国人产品线
working on my African/American line.
我不知道是该取做"黑人逼炸头"
Yeah, I can't decide whether to call it a "Vag-afro"
或是"小毛巴·古丁"
or a "Pube-a Gooding, Jr."
麦克斯 瞧 这些T恤看起来很棒哦
Max, look. These shirts look amazing.
看来我对那家工厂的看法是错的
Well, I guess I was wrong about the factory.
就像曾经我误以为
Like I was wrong about you
你会活不过第一个冬天
making it through that first winter.
瞧 衣服里夹了张纸条
Look, there's a note in here.
肯定是里科写的 他对我非常着迷
Oh, it's probably from Rico. He's obsessed with me.
屁咧 不是他写的
Yeah, it's not from him.
上面写着"帮帮我们"
It says, "Help us."
我就知道有低收入的工人被困在那个黑工厂
Underpaid workers are trapped in that factory, I knew it!
我又一次被冰淇淋蒙蔽了双眼
Once again, I was fooled by ice cream.
没错 这纸条上是写着"帮帮我们"
Yes, it's a note that says, "Help us,"
但我念了这么多年商学院 唯一学到的就是
but if there's one thing I learned in business school,
除非亲眼所见 否则皆不存在
it's if you don't see it, it doesn't exist.
虽然很不想多管闲事 但我们不能袖手旁观啊
Look, as much as we want to, we can't just look away.
我们得跟那些工人谈谈
We need to talk to the workers.
打电话给那个认为你漂亮的人
Call the guy, the one who thinks you're pretty.
我不知道你说的是谁
I don't know who you're talking about.
我只认识一个
I only met a guy who thought
认为我真的真的真的很漂亮的人
I was really, really, really pretty.
我们可以去那家墨西哥店找他们啊
We can meet them at that Mexican place.
墨西哥店那地儿
Ooh, a Mexican place!
我居然忘了拉美市场
I forgot about the Latina market!
姑娘们 麻烦帮我问问
Girls, when you're there,
他们喜不喜欢美墨边界的南边长点毛
find out if they'd be interested in some hair south of the border.
不知道你们俩美女喜欢啤酒还是玛格丽塔
Didn't know if you ladies wanted beers or margaritas,
所以我们给你们点了啤酒丽塔
so we got you Beer-garitas.
一杯要五块钱呢 不过你值这个价
It's five bucks, but you're worth it.
我喜欢好胃口的姑娘
I love a girl with a healthy appetite.
那估计开胃小食没吃完
Well, you're gonna be getting down on one knee
你就要单膝跪地求婚了
before the end of the appetizers.
咱们还是直入主题吧 你在工厂的生活怎么样
So let's just dive right in. How's factory life treating you?
爆点料[低卡鸡尾酒]嘛 在你点啤酒丽塔时
Give us the skinny-- which is what I hope you said
我也希望你会这么说
when you ordered those Beer-garitas,
因为我不想又穷又有小肚腩
'cause I cannot be poor with a muffin top.
我不是很想谈工作
You know, I don't want to talk about work.
你是说你们不准谈论工作的事吗
Oh, are you saying you're not allowed to talk about work?
你的原话我们都听见了哦 里科还是劳乌
Your words, we all heard you, Rico or Raul.
跟我说说 你们俩平时喜欢做什么
Hey, tell me, what do you girls like to do?
我喜欢看着服务员在我餐桌上做鳄梨沙拉
Mm, I like to watch waiters make guacamole at my table.
怎么还不上菜呢
When's that gonna happen?
所以关于工作...
So about work--
好吧
Yeah, okay.
咱们去看看啤酒丽塔好了没
Hey, let's go see what's going on in Beer-garitaville.
我们该怎么办 我根本套不出里科的话
What are we gonna do? I can't get any information out of Rico.
他完全沉浸在
He's so preoccupied with
我超级无敌的美色中
how pretty, pretty, pretty I am.
你好啊 佩吉
Oh, hi, Peggy. How are you?
要不要加入我们 一起聊聊工作呀
Would you like to join us and talk about work?
我们何不聊聊你们俩小婊砸
Why don't we talk about you two skanks
快点滚出这里
gettin' the hell outta here?
看来在烂服务员界 我们被人超越了
And I thought we were bad waitresses.
她叫卡门 也在工厂工作
This is Carmen. She works at the factory too.
我们是死党 她跟我一样 也是其中一名股东
We're BFFs, and she's one of the owners, like me.
没错 她还是里科的唯一股东呢
Yeah, and she's a 100% owner of Rico,
少跟他勾勾搭搭
so hands off.
我们看见你俩坐在这里
We seen you two sittin' over here
好像自己多他妈了不起一样
like you're God's friggin' gift.
可不是嘛 提醒你一句
I know, right? And not for nothing,
里科的斗牛犬不喜欢除我之外的女人哦
but Rico's pit bull doesn't like other girls.
我猜那就是他的斗牛犬吧
I'm guessing that's his pit bull.
还有你 别打劳乌的主意
And you, hands off Raul.
我们之间的爱既深刻 又真实
We have a love that is deep and real,
等他发现这份爱时 一定非常不可思议
and when he finds out about it, it's gonna be magic.
没错
Yup...
跟我想的一模一样
Exactly what I expected.
楼上是欢乐有爱的巧克力工厂
Upstairs is Willy Wonka's factory,
楼下是深受水刑之苦的小奥柏伦柏人
and down here, they're waterboarding Oompa Loompas.
你们好呀 我们只是像往常一样
Yo, what's up? We just comin' here to work
来那边的染房干活了
in the dye room right there as per usual.
就是 没啥大不了的 你们俩看啥子看
Yeah, no biggie. What yous twos lookin' at?
口音学得还挺像
That was a really good accent.
谢谢 我演过歌舞剧《油脂》的里佐
Thanks. I played Rizzo in Grease.
本来应该演女主
Should have been Sandy, but I let
但我把这个角色让给一个跛脚妹子了
but I let the girl with the limp have it.
来吧 把衣服穿上然后进染房
Come on, we have to put these on and go into the dye room,
我猜工厂的秘密一定在里面
'cause I'm guessing that's where it all goes down.
染房 我一点也不意外
The dye room, I'm not surprised.
我一直都知道我们会一起染色[死]
I always knew we'd dye together.
好的 我们只需假装是在这里工作
Okay, we'll just pretend to be working here,
就像我们在餐厅那样
like we do at the diner.
瞧瞧 谁来了
Well, well, look who it is,
装逼婊和装逼婊二号 传奇回归
Stuck-Up and Stuck-Up Two: The Legend Returns.
麦克斯 咱们走吧
Max, we gotta go.
我不能穿着一身死灰色死
My life can't end wearing grey.
怎么了 女士们
What up, ladies?
昨晚才跟我们的男人玩完
Last night, you're hanging with the homies,
今天你们俩就突然穿上工装 能来这里工作了
and today, boom, you just happen to be working here.
这工作来得也太巧了
That's friggin' convenient.
可不是嘛
I know, right?
真是太他妈巧了
Very friggin' convenient.
可不是嘛
I know, right?
我们只需让她们明白谁才是真正的老大
We just have to show them who's boss.
就像我们吓唬住我们烤面包机里的老鼠一样
You know, like we do with the mouse who lives in our toaster.
所以要尖叫着往她们脸上喷玻璃清洁剂吗
So, what, we're gonna scream and then spray Windex at them?
喂 看见这道疤没
Yo! See this scar?
为了一杯冰沙跟五个天主教学生妹动刀打架
Knife fight with five Catholic schoolgirls over a slushie.
除非你们也想尝尝
So unless you want some of what I gave
弗吉尼亚 斯蒂芬妮 拉琪莎 拉托雅
Virginia, Stephanie, Laquetia, Latoya,
和轮椅妹受的苦 否则最好一边凉快去
and the one in the wheelchair, I'd stay clear.
这只是个误会
This is just a misunderstanding.
里科对我不感兴趣
Rico's not interested in me.
他昨晚看着挺喜欢你的呀
Well, he seemed pretty into you last night.
是啊 但那是在她开口说话前
Huh, yeah, but that's before she talked.
拜托 我们对你们的男人完全不感兴趣
Come on, we are not interested in your men at all.
完全不来电 拜托 动动脑好吗
Not at all. I mean, come on.
这话什么意思
What's that mean?
你是说他们有问题吗
You're saying something's wrong with them?
不 她不是那个意思 只是...
No, she's not saying that. It's just--
只是什么
It's just what?
我们才是一对
We're lovers.
你们俩是一对 你们俩看着一点也不...
You two are lovers? 'Cause you don't seem--
我们看着不什么 不像拉拉吗
We don't seem what? Gay?
不 是不够正
No. Hot enough.
这个嘛
Well--
一点儿也不正
Not hot at all.
可不是嘛
I know, right?
快四处看 睁大你的眼睛
Look busy, keep your eyes open.
我想我们已经深入野兽之腹了
I think we're in the belly of the beast.
你们在说我吗
You talkin' about me?
没有
No.
麦克斯 你觉得那扇上锁的门后面是什么
Max, what do you think's behind that locked door?
我就知道 小童工们
I knew it! Toddler slaves.
那些孩子生活在巨大的危险之中
Those kids are in horrible danger
很可能以后会变成... 我
of becoming...me.
快 咱们去那边看看
Come on, let's go over there.
搞什么 你打我
What the-- you hit me!
抱歉抱歉 这是意外
Sorry, so sorry. Accident!
你扔东西像个娘们一样
You throw like a girl.
我就知道 你们俩不是拉拉
See, I knew it, you two aren't gay.
你们俩是想抢我们的男人
Yous are after our guys!
不是的 只是里科觉得我
No, I'm not! Rico just thought I was
真的真的真的很漂亮
really, really, really pretty.
你好大的狗胆
Oh, hell no!
不许欺负我的妞
Leave my lover alone!
开战吧
It's on!
别别别 别开战
It's--no, no, no, no, no! It's not on.
这太傻了 我们不是来抢男人的
This is silly. We're not after anyone.
我们是来帮助那些在这工...
we're here to help some of those work--
没错 现在正式开战
Oh, yeah. Now, it's on!
我警告你
Oh! I warn you!
你个死胖子
Oh, hell no!
不许过来 贱货
Back off, bitch!
你喊谁贱货 贱货
Who you calling bitch, bitch?
亲爱的 你有点玩过头了哦
Honey? You're getting carried away.
现在你真的是被人举过头了
Now you're really getting carried away.
不要 别把我放进烘干机
Oh, no! Don't put me in the dryer!
我以前是有钱人啊 只能干洗
I used to be rich, I'm dry clean only!
你真他妈是找死
That was a big friggin' mistake!
向你们致敬
Respect.
你们俩的战斗力
You two are a lot tougher
比圣布里吉特的学生妹强多了
than those girls from Saint Bridget's.
这是怎么回事
What's happening?
我们来举发你的恶行 我们知道你干的勾当
We're busting you. We know what's happening here.
什么 分红制度和医疗保险吗
What, profit sharing and healthcare?
我们在盒子里发现一张潦草地写着"帮帮我们"的纸条
We found a note in our box with "Help us" scrawled on it.
你该作何解释
How do you explain that?
你有看背面吗
Did you read the back?
"帮帮我们
"Help us..
也是帮帮你自己
Help you...
在美国王牌发挥你全方位的潜力"
to your full potential at American Ace."
我们在每一个盒子里都放了一张
We put one in every box we ship.
看来以后我得开始学习看字不能光看第一句
I have got to start reading more than the first sentence of stuff.
对不起 这都是我的错
I'm sorry, this is all my fault.
我只是一厢情愿地希望
I guess I just wanted to believe
有些孩子的童年会过得比我悲惨
some kids were having a worse childhood than I was.
麦克斯 别内疚 你以为有人需要帮助
Max, don't feel bad. You thought someone needed help,
而你关心他们 这说明你是个好人
and you cared, and that makes you a good person,
我为你感到骄傲
and I'm proud of you.
我都道歉了 你不用这么刻薄吧
I said I was sorry. You don't have to be mean.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我第一批假发到货了
I just got my first shipment of wigs.
苏菲 你干嘛走路姿势怪怪的
Sophie, why are you walking like that?
我不光是老板
Well, I'm not just the president,
我也是用户啊
I'm also a client.
苏菲 你好像有东西掉了
Sophie, I think you dropped something,
除非我看走眼 是巨型波斯蟑螂又出现了
unless we have those giant Persian roaches again.
那画面就连白内障的我也觉得不忍直视
Even a milky version of that was too much.
麦克斯 或许某天会有一个像你这样的人
You know, Max, maybe someday, someone like you will come
冲进这家沙门氏菌工厂 把咱俩救出去
into this Salmonella factory and rescue us.
你在支票后面写什么啊
What are you writing on those checks?
"帮帮我们"
"Help us."
我们在这里工作就暗示着"我们需要帮助"啊
We work here. The "Help us" is implied.